Kelsey's office. Three o'clock. She said to
come alone.
The door's shut. The air is thick.
uniform.
My blood runs cold, my hands go numb. I can't feel
my own chair. He's holding out a folded sheet.
This isn't fair. He looks at me. His face is grim.
He starts to read the line. He doesn't know the
words he holds are a trigger to my mind. Fine.
Are you Aubrey Jordan Fuller? Stop the press!
That is not my name! Stop the press! She's won the
game! He's here! She's won! The walls are gone!
No! No! No! No! No!
No! No! No! No! No! No!
Can't breathe. Can't see. Rocking. Shaking!
King! King! Shaking! The lights are bright! The
world is breaking! King! King! King! King! He's
just a man. A uniform. He's just her. He's her in
here.
Are you Aubrey Jordan Fuller? SYSTEM CRASHED!
THAT IS NOT MY NAME! SYSTEM CRASHED! SHE'S WON
THE GAME! HE'S HERE! SHE'S WON! THE WALLS ARE
GONE! NO! NO! NO! NO!
No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No!
No! No! No!
No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No!
No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No!
No! No! No! No! No! No!